MERIEME EL GOUSSAIRI

Software engineer

Profile

Talented software engineer with over 2 years of experience in teaching high school students the basics of software engineering. In search of a position as a Software Engineer where I can express my creative interests along with applying my technical skillset.

Education

Master degree in IT and modeling of complex systems

Sciences and technologies Faculty, SETTAT

Teaching certification

Sep 2020 _ Mar 2021

Sep 2020 – July 2022

Regional Center for Education and Training Professions, CASABLANCA

Bachelor degree in computer engineering

Sep 2017 – July 2020

Sciences and technologies Faculty, SETTAT

Baccalaureate in physical and chemical sciences

Doukkala heigh school, ELJADIDA

Sep 2016 – July 2017

Employment

software engineer teacher

Sep 2021 – present

Jun 2020 – Mar 2020

Moroccan government, Casablanca

End-of-studies project internship

OPTech, Casablanca

Personal details

Adresse

Res al amane gh27 imm216 appt 8 ain sebaa, casablanca

Phone

+212 708037661

E-mail

Meriemelgoussairi@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/meri eme-el-goussairi-82538215b/

Skills

- Teamwork
- Creative thinking
- Analytical thinking
- Java
- Python
- Web programming
- Operating systems software
- Deep learning
- Machine learning
- SQL/PLSQL
- MySQL
- Microsoft Office

Languages

• English: Medium

• French: Medium

Arabic : Native